接下来我们来构建UI  首先从构造MainActivity的框架开始
To build out our UI, let's start with the wire frames for the main activity.
主界面显示了一个预报列表  里面的每个元素都包含一个图标
It displays a list of forecasts where each item contains an icon,
一个日期  天气描述  还有当天的最高温和最低温
a date, weather description, as well as high and low temperatures for that day.
由于今天的天气对于用户来说是最重要的
Since today's weather is probably most relevant to the user,.
所以和其他日期的数据相比我们更加凸显它的位置
We give more prominence to it as the list item compared to the other dates.
我们首先构造显示未来日期的天气的列表布局
We'll start off by building the list item layout for future dates because
因为它们相对来说比较简单  然后再返回来完成“今天天气”的布局
it's simpler and then afterwards we'll come back to do the today layout.
在forecastLayout的xml文件中  目前的实现是
In the current implementation the list item forecast layout xml.
水平的LinearLayout  里面包含了4个TextView
Is a horizontal, linear layout of four text views.
我们要修改布局  使它能像这个框架一样
We'll need to modify the layout so that it looks like this wire frame.
我们要将布局
We should divide and
拆分成更为基本的元素  拆分到我们能够用所熟悉的布局实现为止
conquer until we can use the view group layouts that we're familiar with.
你能想象将UI拆分成你能够简单实现的小模块的
Can you imagine how you'd break down this UI into components that you
感觉吗？
know how to build?
给个提示  我要是在这加个分隔怎么样呢？
As a hint, what if I draw these separators here?
对于这里面的元素  你能找到方法用熟悉的View Group
Within those elements, can you find a way to break it down
将其进一步拆分吗
even further with view groups you're familiar with?
你需要用到多层viewgroup  也就是ViewGroup里面
You'll need nested view groups which means view groups
包含着ViewGroup
with children view groups.
顺带说一句  用下面的指导信息来命名View ID  这样你的代码
By the way, use the view id names that we provide in the instructor notes below
就能和我们一致了
so that your code will match ours.
要验证布局的实现是否正确  在控件属性中
To verify that the layout is being built correctly,
加一些文本数据
hard code some text values into the fields.
比如date设置为“tomorrow”  weatherCondition设置为“Clear”
Such as tomorrow for the date, or clear for the weather condition.
对于图片  我们可以用ic_launcher作为示例图片
For images, we can specify a placeholder drawable called ic_launcher.
它是启动时用到的图标
It's named this way because it's the launcher icon.
而且也是程序在菜单里显示的图标  并且已经包含在程序源码中了
Which is also known as the app icon and this is already included in our app.
在课程后面的部分  我们会获得其他的
We'll be getting to the rest of the weather icons for
天气图标
our app later in this lesson.
如果你想知道布局是什么样的
If you want to see what this layout looks like,
你可以点击design窗格来进行预览
you can click on the design pane to see a preview of it.
在右侧我们能看到一个树形列表包含了各种各样的view
On the right we see a component tree listing out the different views.
同时我们还能看到View的属性有哪些  对应的值是什么
We can also see for a given view what the properties are and their values.
我们还能调整预览设备的屏幕方向
We can change the orientation of the device that you're previewing.
你也可以选择不同的设备  比如Nexus7 或者Nexus 10
You can also select different devices, such as Nexus 7 or Nexus 10.
你也可以同时预览不同屏幕大小的效果
You can also preview multiple devices at the same time.
这个任务你仅仅是构建布局  所以不要担心字体颜色
As you build out your layout for this task, don't worry about the font color
字体大小或者其他显示细节的问题
or font size, or any other visual details until later.
当你编译运行时  程序应该是这样的
After you compile and run, the app should look something like this.
每个列表项的数据是相同的
Every list item has the same dummy data.
当你改变布局时
When you change the layout,
它会崩溃因为你之前的代码默认认为每个列表项
it will actually cause a crash in your app because your code previously assumed
只有一个TextView
that this list item layout only had one text view.
所以接下来你需要转向ForecastAdapter.java文件
So you'll need to go to the ForecastAdapter.java file.
将bindview方法里的代码注释掉
And comment out the lines of code in the bindview method.
在后面的视频中我们会解决这个问题
We're going to fix this method in a later video.